{
    "QuestionSets": [
	{
    "SetNo":1,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "SetNo":2,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "SetNo":3,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "SetNo":4,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "SetNo":5,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
},
{
    "SetNo":6,
    "Total":2,
    "Questions": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "How old are you?",
            "isMC": false,
            "option": {
                "A": "null",
                "B": "null",
                "C": "null",
                "D": "null"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "100",
            "imgPath": "null"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "When TSK is founded?",
            "isMC": true,
            "option": {
                "A": "1960",
                "B": "1961",
                "C": "1962",
                "D": "1963"
            },
            "CorrectAns": "C",
            "imgPath": "null"
        }
    ]
} ]
}